fedoraforum.org 2009-06-17

# FedoraForum.org - Privacy Policy

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

|  |  |   | FedoraForum.org  
---|---|---  
 **Privacy Policy**  
| User Name |  | Remember Me?  
---|---|---  
Password |  |   
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  

Notices  
---  
  
Hi Unregistered, 

Update:

The F11 golden release is here! So far, the stampede we expected hasn't arrived. As expected, F11 has not been entirely trouble free, but most folks are having little or no trouble with it, and installs are going smoothly. 

Remember folks, fedora is a bit of a cutting edge FOSS based distro, so system requirements may well include a sense of adventure and a willingness to fiddle and futz a bit to get things like you want them.

_However, one issue seems to be consistent. for those installing from the liveCDs, check the announcement about partitioning requirements!_

So far, increased loads haven't been a problem, but if that situation develops, we will still restrict features as we had planned. 

Thank you for your patience and your continued support of both fedora and the fedora forum. 

Dan

Registered (and logged in) members may eliminate this message  
after reading, by clicking the word, "Dismiss" in the upper right corner.  

|  **» Stats**  
---  
Members: 141,806  
Threads: 205,418  
Posts: 1,164,737  
Top Poster: [bob](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=4602) (15,428)  
  
Newest Member [chhay](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=154079)  
  
**»[Latest Forum Posts](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/search.php)**  
---  
  
[USB TV Card firmware...](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=215092 "I am the proud owner of an ASUS My Cinema U3100 TV card \(it's a USB dongle\) which I plugged into laptop #1 running Ubuntu 8.10, the appropriate light became green and I was able to start watching the various delights that is TV nowadays almost immediately. 
 
I normally use Fedora 10 
 
I thought...")

2009-02-27 06:55 AM CST

by [saywot](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=78411)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228313#post1228313) Last post by [eagleton](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=215092)

Today 12:44 AM CDT

13 Replies, 569 Views  
  
[Fedora 11 is out - your...](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=223190 "i'm downloading Fedora 11 live cd now... once finished i'm gonna have a look into it and see if i want to upgrade \(most probably fresh install\) but i want to know who has already installed it and how do you find it so far? 
 
cheers")

2009-06-09 02:14 PM CDT

by [manuleka](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=144032)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228312#post1228312) Last post by [GreyWizzard](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=223190)

Today 12:33 AM CDT

168 Replies, 5,694 Views  
  
[enabling bcm43xx...](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=208507 "Hi .Im a brand new Lnux user trying to get my broadcom bcm4315 usb wireless adapter up in Fedora 10 \(after googling thru numerous sources \)These are the steps that I have followed so far \(without success\) 
1\)downloaded the bcm43xx driver firmware from the following link:...")

2008-12-22 05:11 AM CST

by [girish_rvd](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=137948)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228311#post1228311) Last post by [Transformer](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=208507)

Today 12:33 AM CDT

21 Replies, 2,566 Views  
  
[PDF Files](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=224114 "Hi, I just recently moved to fedora 10 KDE, and KOffice does not allow me to create a pdf file. In fact, I don't know if I ever made one before. I searched around a bit, and downloaded PDFEdit, but it wont allow me to create one, only open files. 
 
Are there any good programs for this that I don't...")

Today 12:22 AM CDT

by [swimi](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=154076)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228310#post1228310) Last post by [swimi](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=224114)

Today 12:33 AM CDT

2 Replies, 7 Views  
  
[help with ntfs-config](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=224116 "Hi,  
Im getting some errors with ntfs-config on Fedora 11.  
This is what appears on the terminal  
 
Traceback \(most recent call last\): 
  File "/usr/bin/ntfs-config", line 41, in <module> 
    from NtfsConfig.NtfsConfig import * 
ImportError: No module named NtfsConfig.NtfsConfig 
 
Any solution?")

Today 12:32 AM CDT

by [gauthamts](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=153903)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228309#post1228309) Last post by [gauthamts](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=224116)

Today 12:32 AM CDT

0 Replies, 2 Views  
  
[compiz-0.8.3 repo for...](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?t=173317 "Many thanks to drhilbert  , LordMorgul  and  neogranas for donating the web space and bandwidth for the compiz-fusion repo   
 
Compiz fusion mirrors 
 
http://www.dfm.uninsubria.it/compiz/fusion/ 
 
http://www.lordmorgul.net/pub/compiz/fusion/ 
 
http://mirror.thegamingkid.com/compiz/fusion/")

2007-11-08 05:40 AM CST

by [leigh123linux](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?u=78273)

[](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/showthread.php?p=1228307#post1228307) Last post by [M4rc0](http://forums.fedoraforum.org/member.php?find=lastposter&t=173317)

Today 12:30 AM CDT

1,995 Replies, 220,188 Views  
  
| Privacy Policy  
---  
The following policy outlines the types of information that we gather about you and the way that way we use and don't use this information.

The information that we collect about our visitors falls into three general categories:

1\. Information You Provide to Us. We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply to us either on the FedoraForum.org site, via e-mail, or in any other way. Some examples of this type of information include the information you submit (such as your name or e-mail address) when you register for FedoraForum.org membership, information that you post on message boards, and information contained in search requests or questions you submit to the site. If you decline to supply or provide us with certain information, we may not be able to provide you with some services that are dependent on the collection of this information.

2\. Information that is Automatically Collected. We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through the FedoraForum.org site. For example, to enhance your experience at FedoraForum.org, we use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie." Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use our site, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of our site where you have entered preference information before. Another example of information that we automatically collect as you navigate our site is information about your computer's connection to the Internet. This information allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on our site.

3\. Information from Other Sources. FedoraForum.org may also obtain information about you from third parties or other sources and may combine the information that we receive from them with information we have already obtained about you.

FedoraForum.org includes links to other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

Questions on Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about the children's privacy statement, the privacy practices of the FedoraForum.org site, or your dealings with FedoraForum.org, please contact us.  
  
Powered by [vBadvanced](http://vbadvanced.com/) CMPS v3.0.1

All times are GMT -7. The time now is 12:47 AM CDT.   

|  |
